Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - M
        - Middleton, Tom - A Jedi's night out (Disc three), 1999; SR-22153; Middleton, Tom (Box 358)
          In same jacket as # SR-22151; SR-22152. Triple album.
          Catalog # MMLLP027; A-side Matrix # MLV-005-E
        - Midfield General - Devil in sports casual, 1997; SR-22154; Midfield General (Box 358)
          In same jacket as # SR-22155. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # SKINT 27; A-side Matrix # SKINT 27 AA1
          Skint
        - Midfield General - Devil in sports casual, 1997; SR-22155; Midfield General (Box 358)
          In same jacket as # SR-22154. 2 copies.
        - Midfield General - Stings in love, 1996; SR-22156; Midfield General (Box 358)
          Catalog # SKINT 10; A-side Matrix # SKINT-10-A
        - Midfield General - Devil in sports casual, 1997; SR-22157; Midfield General (Box 358)
          Catalog # SKINT 27; A-side Matrix # SKINT 27 A
        - Midler, Bette - Hang on in there baby, 1979; SR-22158; Midler, Bette (Box 358)
          In same jacket as # SR-22159. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DSKO 201; A-side Matrix # ST-DK-37464-1
        - Midler, Bette - Hang on in there baby, 1979; SR-22159; Midler, Bette (Box 358)
          In same jacket as # SR-22158. 2 copies.
        - Midler, Bette - I'm beautiful, 1996; SR-22160; Midler, Bette (Box 358)
          Catalog # PRO-A-9591; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-9591-A-SR1
        - Midney, Boris - D-d-d-dance, 1983; SR-22161; Midney, Boris (Box 358)
          Catalog # KM 3891; A-side Matrix # KM-3891 A
          MI
        - Midnight Movers - Truckin', 2005; SR-22162; Midnight Movers (Box 358)
          Catalog # DEL LP 0036; A-side Matrix # DEL LP 0036 A
        - Midnight Star - 90 days (same as cash), 1988; SR-22163; Midnight Star (Box 358)
          Catalog # 4Z9 74501; A-side Matrix # XSS-74501A
          Solar
        - Midnight Star - Scientific love, 1984; SR-22164; Midnight Star (Box 358)
          Catalog # ED 5035; A-side Matrix # STED-5035A-2
        - Midnight Star - Wet my whistle, 1983; SR-22165; Midnight Star (Box 358)
          In same jacket as # SR-22166. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ED 4933; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-4933-A 1
        - Midnight Star - Wet my whistle, 1983; SR-22166; Midnight Star (Box 358)
          In same jacket as # SR-22165. 2 copies.
        - Midnight Star - Freak-a-zoid, 1983; SR-22167; Midnight Star (Box 358)
          Catalog # 0-67919; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-0-67919-A
        - Midnight Star - No parking (on the dance floor), 1983; SR-22168; Midnight Star (Box 358)
          Catalog # ED 4954; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-4954-A1
        - Midnight Star - No parking (on the dance floor), 1983; SR-22169; Midnight Star (Box 358)
          Catalog # ED 4970; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-4970 A
        - Midnight Star - Stay here by my side, 1986; SR-22170; Midnight Star (Box 358)
          Catalog # ED 5225; A-side Matrix # STED-5225-A-1
        - Midnight Star - Operator, 1984; SR-22171; Midnight Star (Box 358)
          In same jacket as # SR-22172. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ED 5018; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-66931 A-2
        - Midnight Star - Operator, 1984; SR-22172; Midnight Star (Box 358)
          In same jacket as # SR-22171. 2 copies.
        - Midnight Star - Freak-a-zoid, 1983; SR-22173; Midnight Star (Box 358)
          In same jacket as # SR-22174. Different discs.
        - Midnight Star - Freak-a-zoid, 1983; SR-22174; Midnight Star (Box 358)
          In same jacket as # SR-22173. Different discs.
          Catalog # ED 4907; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-0-67919-A
        - Midnight Star - Midas touch, 1986; SR-22175; Midnight Star (Box 358)
          Catalog # ED 5164; A-side Matrix # STED-5164-A 1
        - Midnight Star - I've been watching you, 1981; SR-22176; Midnight Star (Box 358)
          Catalog # AS-11505; A-side Matrix # AS-11505-A
        - Midnite - U' Know, 2000; SR-22177; Midnite (Box 358)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # MIDNITE
          Sniper Productions
        - Miers, Mykill - Soul seachin | Net weight, 1995; SR-22178; Miers, Mykill; Phil the Agony (Box 358)
          Catalog # S-32796; A-side Matrix # S-32796
          Immortal Records
        - Mighty Bread - Love me night & day, 1980; SR-22179; Mighty Bread (Box 358)
          Catalog # HJL 004; A-side Matrix # MB-004-A
        - Mighty Diamonds - Knowledge, 1982; SR-22180; Mighty Diamonds (Box 358)
          Catalog # DSR-3903; A-side Matrix # D-S-R-3903-A-SPIDERMAN
          Music Works Records
          Kingston, Jamaica
        - Mighty Dub Katz - It's just another groove, 1995; SR-22181; Mighty Dub Katz (Box 358)
          Catalog # ECB 7; A-side Matrix # ECB7-AA1
          Southern Fried Records
        - Mighty Fire - Sixth street (turn it up), 1982; SR-22182; Mighty Fire (Box 358)
          Catalog # AS-11556; A-side Matrix # AS-11556-A3-SP
        - Mighty Gabby - Hit it, 1983; SR-22183; Mighty Gabby (Box 358)
          Catalog # ICE 12 83 004; A-side Matrix # ICE 12-830004-A
          ICE
        - Mighty Gabby - Hit it, 1983; SR-22184; Mighty Gabby (Box 358)
        - Mighty Gabby - Boots, 1983; SR-22185; Mighty Gabby (Box 358)
          Catalog # ICE 12 83 003; A-side Matrix # ICE 830003-A
        - Mighty Loverboy and the Superheroes - We've got to fight drugs together; Get out of Kuwait Saddam, 1991; SR-22186; Mighty Loverboy and the Superheroes (Box 358)
          Catalog # SSR-620; A-side Matrix # SSR 620 A
          TASO
          Woodside, New York
        - Mighty Mouth - Hollywood party, 1987; SR-22187; Mighty Mouth (Box 358)
          Catalog # D-283; A-side Matrix # D 283 A2
          Fantasy
        - Mighty Pope - Sweet blindness; Because the night, 1979; SR-22188; Mighty Pope (Box 358)
          Catalog # DRCS 8885; A-side Matrix # DRCS-8885-XCN-0223-S-M1
        - Mighty Swallow - Fusion, 1986; SR-22189; Mighty Swallow; Swallow (Box 358)
          Catalog # SCR 389; A-side Matrix # SCR 389 A RE1
        - Mighty Swallow - Town mash down, 1985; SR-22190; Mighty Swallow; Swallow (Box 358)
          Catalog # SCR 364; A-side Matrix # SCR 364 A RE1
        - Mighty Swallow - Party in space, 1983; SR-22191; Mighty Swallow; Swallow (Box 358)
          Catalog # SCR 324; A-side Matrix # SCR-324-A-RE-3
        - Miilkbone - Where'z da' party at?, 1995; SR-22192; Miilkbone (Box 358)
          Catalog # Y 7243 8 58446 1 4; A-side Matrix # Y1-58446-Z1
        - Miilkbone - Where'z da' party at?, 1995; SR-22193; Miilkbone (Box 358)
          Catalog # PRO-79656; A-side Matrix # SPRO-79656-Z1
        - Mi'kal, Jamielah - Our life together, 1985; SR-22194; Mi'kal, Jamielah (Box 358)
          Catalog # CM 536; A-side Matrix # CM 536A
          Clarence Music Records
        - Mike & Charlie - Body rock, 1997; SR-22195; Mike & Charlie (Box 358)
          Catalog # JFR-005; A-side Matrix # JFR005-9709X35-A
          Just Funk In Florida
          Sarasota, Florida
        - Mike & Charlie - The hop | Trippin' in the light, 1998; SR-22196; Mike & Charlie; NV (Box 358)
          Catalog # JFR 007; A-side Matrix # JFR-007-A
        - Mike & Charlie - I get live, 1998; SR-22197; Mike & Charlie (Box 358)
          Catalog # JFR-006; A-side Matrix # MAC-JFR-006
        - Mike & Charlie - In your soul, 1999; SR-22198; Mike & Charlie (Box 358)
          In same jacket as # SR-22199. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JFR-013; A-side Matrix # JFR-013-9905X37-A
        - Mike & Charlie - In your soul, 1999; SR-22199; Mike & Charlie (Box 358)
          In same jacket as # SR-22198. 2 copies.
        - Mike and Ike - Feel this; Plutonic, 1999; SR-22200; Mike and Ike (Box 358)
          Catalog # DGTL 001; A-side Matrix # DGTL-001-A
          Digital Konfusion
        - Mike Boogie - Food around the corner, 2000; SR-22201; Mike Boogie (Box 358)
          Catalog # TT 002; A-side Matrix # TT-002-A
          Tabletools
        - Mikey D & the LA Posse - I get rough; Go for it, 1987; SR-22202; Mikey D & the LA Posse; Mikey-D; L.A. Posse (Box 358)
          Catalog # PA 012; A-side Matrix # PA-012-A
        - Mikey D & the LA Posse - I get rough; Go for it, 1987; SR-22203; Mikey D & the LA Posse; Mikey-D; L.A. Posse (Box 358)
        - Mikey D & the LA Posse - Out of control; Comin' in the house, 1988; SR-22204; Mikey D & the LA Posse; Mikey-D; L.A. Posse (Box 358)
          Catalog # SLX-40137X; A-side Matrix # SLX-40137-X
        - Mikey Dread - Pave the way, 1984; SR-22205; Mikey Dread (Box 358)
          Catalog # HB-31; A-side Matrix # HB-31-A
          Heartbeat Records
          Cambridge, Massachusettes
        - Mikki Bleu - I promise, 1989; SR-22206; Mikki Bleu (Box 359)
          Catalog # MIC 11193; A-side Matrix # SPRO-1-04405-Z1
        - Mikko - 9 to 5, 1998; SR-22207; Mikko (Box 359)
          Catalog # 925-1; A-side Matrix # 925-1-A1
          White Label Music
        - Mil - Ride out, 2001; SR-22208; Mil (Box 359)
          Catalog # JDAB-42872-1; A-side Matrix # JDAB-42872-1A
        - Mild Mannered Janitors - Suck my mother, 1998; SR-22209; Mild Mannered Janitors (Box 359)
          Catalog # FABR019T; A-side Matrix # FEBR-019T-A1
          Fused & Bruised
        - Miles, Buddy - We got to live together, 1970; SR-22210; Miles, Buddy (Box 359)
          Catalog # SR-61313; A-side Matrix # SR 61313-A-M2
        - Miles, Buddy - A message to the people, 1970; SR-22211; Miles, Buddy (Box 359)
          Catalog # SRM1-608; A-side Matrix # SR 61334-A-M1
        - Miles, Robert - Freedom, 1997; SR-22212; Miles, Robert; Sledge, Kathy (Box 359)
          Catalog # 74321 536951; A-side Matrix # 74321-53695-1-A2
          Deconstruction
        - Milian, Christina - Say I, 2006; SR-22213; Milian, Christina; Young Jeezy (Box 359)
          Catalog # ISLR 16488-1; A-side Matrix # BOOO6316-11A
        - Milian, Christina - Dip it low, 2004; SR-22214; Milian, Christina (Box 359)
          Catalog # ISLR 16030-1; A-side Matrix # ISLR-16030-1A
        - Milian, Christina - Dip it low, 2003; SR-22215; Milian, Christina (Box 359)
          In same jacket as # SR-22216. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ISLR-15959; A-side Matrix # ISLR-15959-1A
        - Milian, Christina - Dip it low, 2003; SR-22216; Milian, Christina (Box 359)
          In same jacket as # SR-22215. 2 copies.
        - Milian, Christina - Dip it low, 2004; SR-22217; Milian, Christina (Box 359)
          Catalog # ISLR 16168-1; A-side Matrix # ISLR-16168-1A
        - Milian, Christina - Whatever u want, 2004; SR-22218; Milian, Christina (Box 359)
          Catalog # ISLR 16157-1; A-side Matrix # ISLR 16157-1
        - Miller, Jack - Rockers rising, 1979; SR-22219; Miller, Jack (Box 359)
          Catalog # HLPS0118; A-side Matrix # L-593
          Haiku Music
          Dana Point, California
        - Miller, Jack - Keeper of the gate, 1984; SR-22220; Miller, Jack (Box 359)
          Catalog # HLPS0120; A-side Matrix # HLPS 0120-A
        - Miller, Jack - Dreadlock rock, 1981; SR-22221; Miller, Jack (Box 359)
          Catalog # HLPS0119; A-side Matrix # L-5023
        - Miller, Laurie - Parallels, 1987; SR-22222; Miller, Laurie (Box 359)
          Catalog # DMD 1061; A-side Matrix # STDM-52009-1
        - Milli Mae - My baby daddy, 2005; SR-22223; Milli Mae (Box 359)
          In same jacket as # SR-22224. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 82876-69806-1; A-side Matrix # 82876-69806-1A
        - Milli Mae - My baby daddy, 2005; SR-22224; Milli Mae (Box 359)
          In same jacket as # SR-22223. 2 copies.
        - Milli Vanilli - Baby don't forget my number, 1988; SR-22225; Milli Vanilli (Box 359)
          In same jacket as # SR-22226. 2 copies.
          Catalog # COOLX 178; A-side Matrix # COOLX178 1211 A-2
        - Milli Vanilli - Baby don't forget my number, 1988; SR-22226; Milli Vanilli (Box 359)
          In same jacket as # SR-22225. 2 copies.
        - Milli Vanilli - 2 x 2, 1989; SR-22227; Milli Vanilli (Box 359)
          In same jacket as # SR-22228. 2 copies.
          Catalog # CTLPD 11; A-side Matrix # CTLPD 11 A1
        - Milli Vanilli - 2 x 2, 1989; SR-22228; Milli Vanilli (Box 359)
          In same jacket as # SR-22227. 2 copies.
          Catalog # CTLPD 11; A-side Matrix # CTLPD 11 C1
        - Milliato - Groove on, 1998; SR-22229; Milliato; Half-A-Mill; A.Z. (Box 359)
          Catalog # BBR 777001; A-side Matrix # BBR 777001-A
          Brooklyn Bound Recordings
        - Mills, Eleanore - Mr. Right, 1987; SR-22230; Mills, Eleanore (Box 359)
          Catalog # VMR 007; A-side Matrix # VMR-007-A
          Vinylmania
        - Mills, Stephanie - Rising desire, 1985; SR-22231; Mills, Stephanie (Box 359)
          Catalog # L33-17130; A-side Matrix # MCA-5567-B66
        - Mills, Stephanie - I have learned to respect the power of love, 1986; SR-22232; Mills, Stephanie (Box 359)
          Catalog # L33-17110; A-side Matrix # MCA-5390 BG-1
        - Mills, Stephanie - Stand back, 1985; SR-22233; Mills, Stephanie (Box 359)
          Catalog # L33-17076; A-side Matrix # MCA-5023 BG2
        - Mills, Stephanie - What cha gonna do with my lovin', 1979; SR-22234; Mills, Stephanie (Box 359)
          Catalog # TCD-86; A-side Matrix # TCD 86 AS A 1S
          20th Century Fox Records
        - Mills, Stephanie - Greatest hits - in my life, 1987; SR-22235; Mills, Stephanie (Box 359)
          Catalog # 422 832 519-1; A-side Matrix # 422-832-519-1-AS-SP
        - Mills, Stephanie - You can't run from my love, 1983; SR-22236; Mills, Stephanie (Box 359)
          Catalog # 810 337-1; A-side Matrix # 810-337-1-82-CS-388-LONG-PRC-C1-1
        - Mills, Stephanie - Last night, 1982; SR-22237; Mills, Stephanie (Box 359)
          Catalog # NBD 20244; A-side Matrix # NBD 20244 82 CS 262 PRC C1-1
        - Mills, Stephanie - Rising desire; I have learned to respect the power of love, 1985; SR-22238; Mills, Stephanie (Box 359)
          Catalog # MCA-23644; A-side Matrix # MCA-5723-BG2
        - Mick Milk - Half life, 1982; SR-22239; Mick Milk (Box 359)
          Catalog # CY-903; A-side Matrix # CY-903-A
          Cyclops Records
        - Milo and the Kings - Today, 1974; SR-22240; Milo and the Kings (Box 359)
          Catalog # C-9032; A-side Matrix # 9032A
          Camille Records
        - Milton Banana Trio - Samba é Isso, 1977; SR-22241; Milton Banana Trio (Box 359)
          Catalog # 107.0257; A-side Matrix # 107.0257-A
        - Minako - Town, 1982; SR-22242; Minako (Box 359)
          Catalog # AAD-14014; A-side Matrix # M-14014-AS-RE-M1
          Alfa
          Japan
        - Mind Bomb - Metacosmic dimensions | Westwood is a tw*t (allegedly) (disc one), 1996; SR-22243; Mind Bomb; Jeep Beat Collective (Box 359)
          In same jacket as # SR-22244. Double album.
          Catalog # RUF-014; A-side Matrix # RUF-014-A
          The Ruf Label
        - Mind Bomb - Metacosmic dimensions | Westwood is a tw*t (allegedly) (disc two), 1996; SR-22244; Mind Bomb; Jeep Beat Collective (Box 359)
          In same jacket as # SR-22243. Double album.
          Catalog # RUF-014; A-side Matrix # RUF-014-C
        - Miner, Tim - Wouldn't change a thing, 1992; SR-22245; Miner, Tim (Box 359)
          Catalog # 3746310721; A-side Matrix # 37 4C3-10Z2 1A SR1
        - Ming & FS - Fish eyes; Back to one, 2004; SR-22246; Ming & FS (Box 359)
          Catalog # 12SPN6; A-side Matrix # 12SPN6 A
          Spun Records
        - Mingo Lewis - Flight never ending, 1976; SR-22247; Mingo Lewis (Box 359)
          Catalog # PC 34260; A-side Matrix # P AL 34260-1A
        - Mingus, Charles - Town hall concert, 1971; SR-22248; Mingus, Charles; Dolphy, Clifford (Box 359)
          Catalog # JWS-9; A-side Matrix # F-2823-1-A1
        - Ministry - Revenge; I wanted to tell her, 1983; SR-22249; Ministry (Box 359)
          Catalog # AD 1 9062; A-side Matrix # AD1 9062-SA-ES3
        - Ministry - I'm falling, 1982; SR-22250; Ministry (Box 359)
          Catalog # 110072X; A-side Matrix # 110072X
          Wax Trax! Records
        - Ministry - The nature of love, 1985; SR-22251; Ministry (Box 359)
          Catalog # WAX 009; A-side Matrix # WAX 009 A
        - Minmi - T.T.T., 2002; SR-22252; Minmi (Box 359)
          In same jacket as # SR-22253. 2 copies.
          Catalog # NLP-1032; A-side Matrix # NLP-1032A
          Victor
        - Minmi - T.T.T., 2002; SR-22253; Minmi (Box 359)
          In same jacket as # SR-22252. 2 copies.
        - Minnelli, Liza - Losing my mind, 1989; SR-22254; Minnelli, Liza (Box 359)
          Catalog # 49 68858; A-side Matrix # XSS 68858 B-1A
        - Minnelli, Liza - Love pain, 1989; SR-22255; Minnelli, Liza (Box 359)
          Catalog # 49 73166; A-side Matrix # XSS73166A-1A
        - Minogue, Kylie - Wouldn't change a thing, 1989; SR-22256; Minogue, Kylie (Box 359)
          Catalog # 0-21350; A-side Matrix # 0-21350-A
        - Minott, Echo - Gone back again | Babylon bops, 1987; SR-22257; Minott, Echo; Major Worries (Box 359)
          Catalog # LLDIS 0021; A-side Matrix # LLDIS-0021-A
          Live and Love
        - Minott, Lincoln "Sugar" - Buy out the bar; Poor man Pickney, 1983; SR-22258; Minott, Lincoln "Sugar" (Box 359)
          Catalog # LML 13358; A-side Matrix # LML 13358-A-1
          Black Roots
        - Minott, Sugar - Level vibes, 1983; SR-22259; Minott, Sugar (Box 360)
          In same jacket as # SR-22260. Different discs.
          Catalog # TRD 8754; A-side Matrix # TRD 8754-A
          Tad's Record
        - Ranking Prendigas - Murderer, 1983; SR-22260; Ranking Prendigas (Box 360)
          In same jacket as # SR-22259. Different discs.
          Catalog # TRD 4983; A-side Matrix # TRD-4983-A-1
        - Mint Condition - You don't have to hurt no more; Change your mind, 1996; SR-22261; Mint Condition (Box 360)
          Catalog # PSPRO 00375; A-side Matrix # PSPRO 00375 A RE2-SP1
        - Mint Condition - Forever in your eyes, 1991; SR-22262; Mint Condition (Box 360)
          Catalog # 28968 1208 1; A-side Matrix # 28968-1208-1A-SP2
        - Mint Condition - Someone to love, 1994; SR-22263; Mint Condition (Box 360)
          Catalog # 31458 7461 1; A-side Matrix # 31458 7461 1A SP1
        - Mint Condition - So fine, 1994; SR-22264; Mint Condition (Box 360)
          Catalog # 31458 8364 1; A-side Matrix # 31458 8364 1A SP1
        - Mint Condition - Let me be the one, 1997; SR-22265; Mint Condition (Box 360)
          Catalog # PSPRO 00512; A-side Matrix # PSPRO 00512 A
        - Mint Condition - Let me be the one, 1997; SR-22266; Mint Condition (Box 360)
          In same jacket as # SR-22267. 2 copies.
          Catalog # LET 2; A-side Matrix # LET 2 A
        - Mint Condition - Let me be the one, 1997; SR-22267; Mint Condition (Box 360)
          In same jacket as # SR-22266. 2 copies.
        - Mint Condition - Let me be the one, 1997; SR-22268; Mint Condition (Box 360)
          Catalog # LET 1; A-side Matrix # LET 1 A
        - Minutemen - Ok, alright, 1989; SR-22269; Minutemen (Box 360)
          In same jacket as # SR-22270. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TAI 126615; A-side Matrix # TAI-126615-A
          Tuff City Records
        - Minutemen - Ok, alright, 1989; SR-22270; Minutemen (Box 360)
          In same jacket as # SR-22269. 2 copies.
        - Miracle - We ain't scared, 2000; SR-22271; Miracle (Box 360)
          Catalog # UNIR-20257-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20257-1-A
        - Miracle - Find someone new, 1990; SR-22272; Miracle (Box 360)
          Catalog # ZBR 0001; A-side Matrix # NR-19567-A
          Zee-Bra Records
        - Miracle - Bounce, 2000; SR-22273; Miracle (Box 360)
          Catalog # 012156987-1; A-side Matrix # 012156957-1-A
        - Miracles - Doin' Mickey's monkey, 1981; SR-22274; Miracles (Box 360)
          Catalog # M5-217V1; A-side Matrix # M5-217V1-A-08A
        - Mirage - Serious mix 2, 1987; SR-22275; Mirage (Box 360)
          Catalog # BC 12-2040-40; A-side Matrix # DM B-8798 A-4/8-87
          BCM Records
        - Miranda - Give me your love, 1996; SR-22276; Miranda (Box 360)
          Catalog # SUN 12831; A-side Matrix # SUN12831-A
          Sunshine Entertainment
        - Miranda, Carmen - Carmen Miranda in Hollywood, 1983; SR-22277; Miranda, Carmen (Box 360)
          Catalog # 203 198; A-side Matrix # 203 198 A
          MCA Coral
        - Miranda, Wayne - Helpless, 1979; SR-22278; Miranda, Wayne; Rush Release (Box 360)
          Catalog # R 007; A-side Matrix # RR-7A
          Rockey Records
          Holbrook, New York
        - Miss Jane - It's a fine day, 2000; SR-22279; Miss Jane (Box 360)
          Catalog # RM0104; A-side Matrix # RM-0104-A
          Rampage
        - Missjones - Where I wanna be boy, 1994; SR-22280; Missjones (Box 360)
          Catalog # 53748-0144-0; A-side Matrix # 550144-A RE2
        - Miss Mia - Hate on me, 2004; SR-22281; Miss Mia (Box 360)
          Catalog # L-14618M; A-side Matrix # L-14618M-A
          Moyo Music
          Newark, New Jersey
        - Miss Piggy - Stereau warmup; Exercise your rights | Baby won't cha, 1982; SR-22282; Miss Piggy; Sadane, Marc (Box 360)
          Catalog # PRO-A-1077; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-2-1077-SH1
        - Miss Thang - Thunder and lightning, 1986; SR-22283; Miss Thang (Box 360)
          Catalog # TB 889; A-side Matrix # TB-889-A
        - Miss Thang - Thunder and lightning, 1986; SR-22284; Miss Thang (Box 360)
          In same jacket as # SR-22285. 2 copies.
        - Miss Thang - Thunder and lightning, 1986; SR-22285; Miss Thang (Box 360)
          In same jacket as # SR-22284. 2 copies.
        - Missill - Choose to care, 2006; SR-22286; Missill; PM; Blurum 13 (Box 360)
          Catalog # ER 004; A-side Matrix # ER004-A-
          The Elephant
        - Missing Links - Monkey breaks vol. zero, 1996; SR-22287; Missing Links (Box 360)
          Catalog # L-46087; A-side Matrix # L-46087
          Primeight Records
        - Mission Cartel - Elektrosox, 2002; SR-22288; Mission Cartel; DJ 2 Fresh; DJ Quest (Box 360)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # BA-002 A1
          Breaks Ahead
        - Mission: - Home, 2001; SR-22289; Mission: (Box 360)
          Catalog # PR-075SV; A-side Matrix # PR-074-SV-A
          PUTS Records
        - Mission: - Contagious, 2000; SR-22290; Mission: (Box 360)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # S-45192
          B Sdies Entertainment
        - Mission: - One (disc one), 2001; SR-22291; Mission: (Box 360)
          In same jacket as # SR-22292. Double album.
          Catalog # IUR9011-1; A-side Matrix # IUR 9011-1 A
          Insidious Urban Records
        - Mission: - One (disc two), 2001; SR-22292; Mission: (Box 360)
          In same jacket as # SR-22291. Double album.
          Catalog # IUR9011-1; A-side Matrix # IUR 9011-1 C
        - Mission UK - Wasteland, 1987; SR-22293; Mission UK (Box 360)
          Catalog # PRO 477-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-477-1-2-58922-SHORT-ES2
        - Mission UK - Tower of strength, 1988; SR-22294; Mission UK (Box 360)
          Catalog # PRO 585-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-585-1-2-59545-LP-SP 1-1
        - Mista - Lady (the remixes), 1996; SR-22295; Mista (Box 360)
          Catalog # ED-6015; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-63975-A1
        - Mista - Blackberry molasses, 1996; SR-22296; Mista (Box 360)
          Catalog # ED 5834; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5834-A-1
        - Mista - Blackberry molasses, 1996; SR-22297; Mista (Box 360)
          Catalog # ED 5860; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5860-A-1
        - Mista - Lady, 1996; SR-22298; Mista (Box 360)
          Catalog # ED-5879; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-92414-A-1
        - Mista Grimm - Steady dippen, 1995; SR-22299; Mista Grimm (Box 360)
          Catalog # BAS 7066; A-side Matrix # XSS-7066-A-2A
        - Mista Grimm - Indo smoke, 1993; SR-22300; Mista Grimm (Box 360)